Some secrets should remain buried
City of Tiny Lights is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Pete Travis.
In the teeming, multicultural metropolis of modern-day London, a seemingly straightforward missing-person case
launches a down-at-heel private eye into a dangerous world of religious fanaticism and political intrigue.
Tommy Akhtar, played by Riz Ahmed.
Melody, played by Cush Jumbo.
Lovely, played by James Floyd.
Shelley, played by Billie Piper.
Farzad Akhtar, played by Roshan Seth.
Young Shelley / Emma, played by Hannah Rae.
City of Tiny Lights is a 2016 British crime thriller film directed by Pete Travis and
written by Patrick Neate, based on his own 2005 novel of the same name.
It stars Riz Ahmed, Cush Jumbo, James Floyd, Billie Piper and Roshan Seth.
Set in London, it tells the story of a private detective who
investigates the disappearance of a Russian prostitute.
The film had its world premiere in the Special Presentations section at the
2016 Toronto International Film Festival on 12 September 2016.
It was released in the United Kingdom on 7 April 2017.
The film explores themes of london, england, based on novel or book,
religious fundamentalism, political intrigue , missing person.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and intense.